## CHI CHUNG AU ALVIN AU

**E-mail:** alvinau0427@outlook.com

**Phone:** +852 9860 9486

**Portfolio:** https://alvinau0427.github.io **GitHub:** https://github.com/alvinau0427

## **Professional Summary**

Web / Application developer with 2+ years of experience and proven production support skills. Core technical skills include Java Spring and React. Seeking to develop my skills or bring value to an established organization through testing, deployment, and software debugging.

## **Work Experience**

#### **ICO Limited**

Programmer (Full-time / Consultant), October 2021 - Present

Hong Kong

Company Information: https://www.ico.com.hk/

Secondment Company Information: <a href="https://www.ocbcwhhk.com/personal-banking/en/index.html">https://www.ocbcwhhk.com/personal-banking/en/index.html</a>

- Consultant Programmer at OCBC Wing Hang Bank Limited
- Provided business as usual and production support to the mobile banking application which develop by using Apache Cordova, including ReactJS for web view, Kotlin for Android native app, and Swift for iOS native app
  - Business As Usual (BAU)
    - Provided UAT application builds for users using Jenkins, and Firebase app distribution
    - Implemented bug fixes and developed different features for the mobile banking application
    - Troubleshot potential security issues which were scanned by Fortify Software
  - Internal Production
    - Operated app shielding on production builds using Promon Shield
    - Published the internal app production on Google Play Console and App store

#### **SmarTone Mobile Communications Holdings Limited**

Programmer (Full-time), September 2020 – October 2021 Company Information: https://www.smartone.com/en/home/

Hong Kong

- Participated in the new revamp internal web application project called Enterprise Product Catalog.
  Developed the front-end layout by using AngularJS with API data using Spring boot, and Oracle database
  - Sales Flow and Sales Figure Enquiry
    - Developed the landing page (product categorized) for other team colleagues
    - Delivered the interfaces with graph features for sales figures and transactions
  - Payment
    - Contributed parts of payment feature for displaying chargeable items in an order, filling payment information, and generating special handling fee

#### Principal trust Company (Asia) Limited

IT Service Desk (Summer Work Placement), July 2019 – September 2019

Hong Kong

Company Information: <a href="https://www.principal.com.hk/">https://www.principal.com.hk/</a>

Assisted daily support tasks to the users including Tier 0 and Tier 1 support level

#### **HKT Limited**

PC Field Engineer (Full-time), November 2017 – August 2018

Hong Kong

Company Information: https://www.hkt.com/?locale=en

 Provided PC and server support services including upgrades, data migration, and on-site troubleshooting to different government's sub-office

#### **Education**

## The Open University of Hong Kong

Bachelor of Computing with Honours in Internet Technology, September 2018 – August 2020

## Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education (Tsing Yi)

Higher Diploma in Software Engineering, September 2015 – July 2017

### **Academic Awards**

#### Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education (Tsing Yi)

Outstanding Industrial Attachment Project Award, January 2017

# The China Mainland, Hong Kong and Macao Digital Economy Innovation and Entrepreneurship Competition 2016

Silver Medal Award, October 2016

#### **Skills**

Programming Languages Java, Kotlin, Swift, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL

Frameworks Java EE (Spring MVC, Spring Boot, RESTful API, Hibernate JPA, JSP),

Angular.js, React.js, Node.js

**Databases** Oracle Database, MySQL Server, MongoDB

**Tools** Eclipse, IntelliJ IDEA, NetBeans, Android Studio, XCode, Toad for Oracle,

Postman, Git, JBoss, Docker, Jenkins, Kibana

Language Cantonese (Fluent), Mandarin (Intermediate), English (Intermediate)